Hello.
Where are you from?
From Russia.
Ah, that's clear.  The police.  What city?
Sevastopol.
How do you communicate?   I'm
just chatting, that's all.   Did
you come to Sevastopol after
1914 or did you live there until
1914?
I lived in Sevastopol until I was fourteen
.
Understood.  Where did you put your Ukrainian passport?
Yes, it's somewhere in the closet.
Understood.  That is, they did not abandon it.
Here.
Well, that's how the situation happened.
Cunning, cunning.
Well, that's prudent.  Agree.  A wise
man.  What are you talking about here?
I'm telling you, I just go in with people and
talk.   About
what?   What can we
talk about?
Good question.  Yes.  To you.  Why do you
think
Putin can't protect Crimea from
Ukrainian drone and missile strikes?
Let me send you my previous question.
Why can't Putin protect
oil refinery warehouses in Russia?  [laughter]
Good, good.
Because I will answer you, this is war, and in
war all rules are good.
At the moment,
both sides are suffering.
And this is war.  Where do you live?  You are not in a
fairy tale.  It's a war of light, guys.
There is real light in Sevastopol.  I
watched the video, it was just awful.
How do you poor things survive?  There are a
lot of videos and everything else now.
Yes, there are a
lot of videos in your area and in your
country.   We
had a
lot of videos in 22 years, and now there are a lot of
videos from occupied Crimea, a lot of videos
from Donetsk, Lugansk, Tambov,
Rostov.
And we have a lot of videos.  And do you understand these
videos,
how does it all work?
Why are you really so tired?
Well, what irritates me more is that there is a
movie I recently watched where
aliens attacked people.   Yes.
And the whole world united.
So that
was cool,
huh?  Everything annoys me.
What exactly is annoying?
People should not fight.
Well, maybe with aliens.
Yes, maybe we should fight with them too.   Do
n't you think that in this case,
Russians are like aliens?
Invading someone else's territory, huh?   Is the
whole earth uniting against them?
Seriously?   Yes.   Are
you serious right now?   Yes.
[laughter]
Who did Russia touch initially?
Ukraine, Georgia, Moldova, Syria, and many
others.
Maybe she helped?
Well, somehow she helps in such a way that after
her there are only ruins left.
How else?  So that everyone understands.
Well, no one bombed Crimea before Russia helped
, right?
Who bombed Crimea?
Well, no one bombed Crimea.
In terms of?  Are you saying they bombed
Crimea just now?  And who bombed Crimea?
Ukraine bombed Crimea.
For what?
Because Russia helps.
Understand?  Before Russia came to
help Crimea, I don’t understand.
Look, until 2014, until
Russia came to Crimea to help, no one
bombed Crimea.  Is it true?
Listen, I was in Crimea on Tarkhankut,
but I was little under Ukraine
and I was under Russia.
I asked people:
“So, how do
people
build pitchforks for themselves?”
That is, you are not from Crimea now,
because you say: “I was in Crimea.”  So.
Well, of course.
So where are you from?
From the Moscow region, just to make things
easier for you.
I'm telling you that you are not from Crimea or
Sevastopol.  So.  [snorts] So, look,
before Russia came to Crimea, in
Tarkanhut, everyone was relaxing peacefully and
no one bombed them.  And now
drones are falling on the beach.   Are
you obsessed with war already?
Yes, yes, we are obsessed with war, but it
turns out that this doesn’t make things any easier for the Crimeans
.  Until you, the Russians, came to
help them.   Is
this your revenge on the Crimeans?  I don't understand
.
No, this is our revenge on the Russians.
Through the Crimeans,
through everyone who is for Russia.
What is your name?
Anthony.
Anthony.   This
single-
minded thought of yours will not lead to anything good.  Anthony
from forever and ever, from history to history, will
never bring you to the good that
you want to do.   It was
as if Zhirinovsky had possessed me.
I see, I see.  Yes, it seems he didn't move out
from you.
Well, that's how it will be, I think.  Well no, I see
hatred.  You hide hatred in
your facial expressions.   Yes.
I don't even hide it.
You don't have any peace of mind.
I don't hide my hatred.
Calmness is strength.
But I have no peace, no strength.   It's
just pure, crystalline hatred.   Yes.   Where does
Ukrainians' hatred of
Russians come from?
So that's where I'm coming from,
if Kievan Rus' was
originally
explained.
Well, there was Kievan Rus,
so there was.  So
what next?
Well, and then there was no Kievan Rus.   There
was no Kievan Rus' after that.  Next
came the Tatar-Mongols.   Yes.  Yes.
And there were the Tatars-Mongols, Lithuania and,
in short, the Ruriks and that’s it.  And, in short, it went.
So where did it
come from?  From Saint Petersburg.
No.  So what was your point?  Well, there
were Rurik and
Da, I didn’t want to convey.  I don't want to
report anything.  I am not a historian.  I
know so little about history.
So, why did you bring this up?
Getting caught up
in such a routine in your country.  Why do you need
such a beautiful country?
Although, maybe let it be so.
Listen, explain to me why, in short, it
turns out that now it’s flying through your
Russia?
Why can't you tell the Americans and
the British to stop?
Well, everything has its time.
And how long has Russia been bombed for already 5 years
?  How much longer do we have to
wait?
Who's bombing?
Ukraine.  Well, NATO.  NATO is being bombed by
Ukraine.  NATO is bombing through Ukraine.
Straight from Ukraine?
No, NATO is bombing.
If there was only one Ukraine, then Ukraine would
burn.
It would be, yes, it wouldn’t be, [laughter]
yes, because they always want resources.
This is a hyena.
Well, why can't Putin hit them with his fist
and say: "That's it, stop!"
Because that's how world politics
works.
Explain.   I
can't explain it completely, but I
think so.
Try.
What to try?
Try to explain.
Well, these are a bit difficult for me to explain.
I see, I understand, but try.
Participation in major political events
should be limited to certain states.
Explain.
That means they explain it to you, that
means they have weight.
So, what's the weight?  In Newtons, in
kilograms.  How can we measure its weight?
Fluff.  Heavier than a liter.
[laughter]
So they have weight.  Further,
further, cigarettes.
What is your name?
Anthony.
Brain.  [laughter]
Let's find the tit and continue.
Come on now.   What were
we talking about?  Joke.   Let
's tell a joke.   It's
flying.
Crow.
The crow is
tail first.
Understood?  Well,
not exactly.
Tail first.  The crow is flying.
How does a crow fly like that?   It's
not the point.  The crow flies tail first, and there is
meat on it.
Who are they carrying?  Wait.  Who are they carrying?
Which one are they carrying?
You say they carry the crow.  Is the crow being carried
or is it flying?
The crow flies tail first.
How is this forward?
Backwards.
How can a crow fly backwards?   There
will be no joke.
And this is a joke.  Damn, I thought this was
real.  Let's.
No, that's it, let's move on.
Wait, what are you doing?  A crow is flying.  Understood.  In
the joke, the crow flies sideways.  What next?
Which side?
Well, it
flies backwards.
So,
and then the fox sees the crow.
Fox, do you mean forest?  Like different forests or the
fox that ate the gingerbread man.
Yes, that's it, I got it.  You are uninteresting.  You are a
fox.  Not a fox, but a fox.  So, the fox saw a
crow flying backwards.  Did the fox see her from behind or from
the front?   With an
ordinary glance.   With a
glance.  So, further.
And he asks the Crow:
"Crow,
why are you flying backwards?"
And Vorona answers her:
"Democracy,
indeed."
Alice says: "Holy [ __ ], do you have
democracy there?"
The crow says, "Yes."
Okay, wait, stop, stop.  Uh, at
this point, Vorona is even
talking.
Clear.
Okay, wait.  How can Vorona talk at all
?  Well, flying backwards is
understandable.  Talk how?   Are
you going to listen to a joke or to the factors?
A. I just didn’t quite understand.  Well,
Litsa.  Okay, go ahead.  So.  And what does
she say?
Well, that's the joke.
Ah, I get it.  All.  So, what does she say?
Boring type.   Yes.  Let
's finish the joke.
No, I won't tell you everything.
Damn, they say that whoever doesn't
finish telling a joke,
whoever doesn't finish telling a joke, is the one.  So you
better finish telling me.
You don't include me.  Whoever is being
disappointed, I can
say this.
In short, in general, I got it.  You just forgot
this joke.  It's clear.
No, I haven't forgotten.   Then
tell me.
Well, that joke about Ukraine, it turns out,
when I said that the crow, in short,
speaks to the fox, that’s democracy.  Got it, the
fox talks too,
right?  Yes, the fox is talkative.
She went, in short, I got it.  also backwards
and raised her tail.
And, in short,
he walks and walks, and then the wolf starts
walking backwards like a wolf, or not?
No, the wolf is walking in front [laughter]
and like, let's go to
the forest, and the fox is shouting to the crowd,
right?
And he shouts to the Crow: “I understand, Crow, but what kind of
democracy is this?”  And the Crow shouts to
this very fox.  So, he
says, that’s democracy down there.
Oh, we have democracy at the top, and at the
bottom it will be the same, my dear.
Got it, huh?  Joke.
So, what's the joke?   This
turns out to be a bad joke.
Well, what was its essence supposed to be?
Yes, the point is that the
way people try,
so it will be.
Didn't understand.  Do you have democracy or are you at
the bottom?
I am alone.
That is, you are not there, you are not on Let's do it this way.   Are
you like a crow up there or are you an
ordinary resident down there?
I'm on my own.
Well, that is, like a fox on its own.
Go to hell, you're not a fox.
Okay, wait.  Well, you're not a crow, you're not
on top.
At the top are Putin, Peskov, Lavrov.  Here
they are, the crow, they are at the top.
I'm somewhere near the Wolf.
No, wait, come on, agree.  Uh,
around the wolf - these are the FSB officers, the cops.  Here
they are near the wolf.   Yes.
And you, it seems, if you are not a crow of the highest
echelons of power, if you are not a wolf, right?
This guy is some kind of law enforcement officer,
so it turns out you're a little fox
.
No, put away your acting.
No, well let's do it this way.  Well, the wolf is really the
FSB, yes, the FSB, in short,
then the prosecutor's cops, those have
always been wolves, yes.  Crow -
Well, I have no problems with anything.
I am a self-employed person.  I'm doing my
job and everything is fine with me.   What
kind of work do you do?
In construction.
Understood.  Then comes the test and you are
like a wolf to a wolf.   Yes.   It's
not my business as a wolf.  The technical supervision comes to me
and makes a fox out of you.   That's
it, it's frozen.
The wolf came to him, it seems.
Like, subscribe, comment.  Subscribe to
our WhatsApp channel, here is the QR code.  There,
news similar to that
in the Telegram channel is posted for those who don’t have
Telegram or who don’t use it for
other reasons.  Subscribe to our
WhatsApp channel.